Read and agree with ALL terms of use written in this txt file before using this MikuMikuDance Model Data
If you do not agree with all terms of use, or if you do not understand any part of this terms of use txt file, you are NOT allowed to use this MikuMikuDance Model Data.

Yuuki Asuna
© Kawahara Reki (Dengeki Bunko / Ascii · Media Works)

Modelers:
Akane-Chi00 「あかね」

History
* v1.00x
* v1.02x

Terms of Use:
-Any work like editing and taking parts or transplant this model with other models is not allowed.
-Do not use this MMD Model for works which include obscene, grotesque, &/or violent content.
-Do not use this MMD Model for works which include YAOI/YURI content.
-Do not re-distribute this MMD Model Data.
-Private Trading and Public Trading of this MMD Model Data is NOT allowed.
-Please use this MMD Model Data at your own risk. I can not be held liable or responsible for any damages caused by using this data.
-This model is not permitted for commercial use by any 3rd party.
-This MMD Model Data may not be used for any works which contain negative content toward the original product, individual, &/or group.  
-You are NOT permitted to sell this MMD Model data in ANY format, whether digital or in print.
-Due to massive violation the model has been locked from editing.
-Unlocked model only given to acquaintance of mine.

Useful Links:
http://akane-chi00.deviantart.com/
https://twitter.com/AkaneChi00

Sword Art Online - Ordinal Scale -